homespakistan.com 2017-11-21

# Privacy Policy

At homespakistan.com we are committed to protecting your privacy.

Do we use Cookies?

Cookies must be enabled to purchase online on this store; this is to embrace privacy and security related issues regarding your visit to this site.

By enabling cookie support on your browser, the communication between you and this site is strengthened to be certain it is you who are making transactions on your own behalf, and to prevent leakage of your privacy information. This information is only accessible by us when you are viewing our website.

Will we disclose the information it collects to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade or rent your personal information to others. We may choose to do so in the future with trustworthy third parties, but you can tell us not to by sending an e-mail message requesting your information not being shared with others. We may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns and related site information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics will include no personally identifying information. We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mails, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments and providing customer services. Such companies and individuals will have access to personal information needed to perform these functions, but may not use it for any other purposes and are required to process the data in accordance with the Pakistan's Data Protection legislation.

We are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect on the site to manage customers and processing of orders at www.homespakistan.com possible. We do not sell, trade or rent your personal information to others. We may choose to do so in the future with trustworthy third parties, but you can tell us not to by sending an email.

**Your Consent**

By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by www.homespakistan.com. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we disclose it.

**What information do we collect and how do we use it?**

When you contact us, we need to know your name, address, email address and details of the occasion. This allows us to process and fulfill your request. We also ask for your telephone number, which enables us to contact you urgently if there is a problem with your request. when you order, we need to know your name, address, email address, details of the occasion recipients name, recipients address, delivery address and credit or debit card details. This allows us to process and fulfill your order and to notify you of the status of your order. We may also use the information we collect to occasionally notify you about important functionality changes to the Web site, new hire services and special offers we think you'll find valuable.

**How do we protect customer information?**

When you place orders or request details, we use a secure server. The secure server software (SSL) encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us. Furthermore, as required by the Pakistan Data Protection Legislation, we follow strict security procedures in the storage and disclosure of information, which you have given us, to prevent unauthorized access. Our security procedures mean that we may occasionally request proof of identity before we are able to disclose sensitive information to you.
